<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Scriptor</title>
        <description>Scriptor is a minimal, clean, modern &amp; responsive Jekyll theme for writers</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 22:32:36 +0200</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 22:32:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>Graphic Designer On The Road</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer is a professional within the graphic design and graphic arts industry who assembles together images, typography, or motion graphics to create a piece of design. A graphic designer creates the graphics primarily for published, printed or electronic media, such as brochures (sometimes) and advertising. They are also sometimes responsible for typesetting, illustration, user interfaces, web design, or take a teaching position. A core responsibility of the designer’s job is to present information in a way that is both accessible and memorable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A degree or certificate from an accredited trade school is usually considered essential for a graphic design position. After a career history has been established, though, the graphic designer’s experience and number of years in the business are considered the primary qualifications. A portfolio, which is the primary method for demonstrating these qualifications, is usually required to be shown at job interviews, and is constantly developed throughout a designer’s career. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Graphic_designer&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ice molecules can exhibit up to sixteen different phases &lt;em&gt;(packing geometries)&lt;/em&gt; that depend on temperature and pressure. When water is cooled rapidly (quenching), up to three different types of amorphous ice can form depending on the history of its pressure and temperature. When cooled slowly correlated proton tunneling occurs below 20 K giving rise to macroscopic quantum phenomena. Virtually all the ice on Earth’s surface and in its atmosphere is of a hexagonal crystalline structure denoted as ice Ih (spoken as “ice one h”) with minute traces of cubic ice denoted as ice Ic. The most common phase transition to ice Ih occurs when liquid water is cooled below 0°C (273.15K, 32°F) at standard atmospheric pressure. It may also be deposited directly by water vapor, as happens in the formation of frost. The transition from ice to water is melting and from ice directly to water vapor is sublimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;characteristics&quot;&gt;Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a naturally-occurring crystalline inorganic solid with an ordered structure, ice is considered a mineral.[citation needed] It possesses a regular crystalline structure based on the molecule of water, which consists of a single oxygen atom covalently bonded to two hydrogen atoms, or H-O-H. However, many of the physical properties of water and ice are controlled by the formation of hydrogen bonds between adjacent oxygen and hydrogen atoms; while it is a weak bond, it is nonetheless critical in controlling the structure of both water and ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ice contains no future , just the past, sealed away. As if they’re alive, everything in the world is sealed up inside, clear and distinct. Ice can preserve all kinds of things that way- cleanly, clearly. That’s the essence of ice, the role it plays.” 
&lt;cite&gt;― Haruki Murakami&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unusual property of ice frozen at atmospheric pressure is that the solid is approximately 8.3% less dense than liquid water. The density of ice is 0.9167 g/cm3 at 0 °C,[4] whereas water has a density of 0.9998 g/cm³ at the same temperature. Liquid water is densest, essentially 1.00 g/cm³, at 4 °C and becomes less dense as the water molecules begin to form the hexagonal crystals[5] of ice as the freezing point is reached. This is due to hydrogen bonding dominating the intermolecular forces, which results in a packing of molecules less compact in the solid. Density of ice increases slightly with decreasing temperature and has a value of 0.9340 g/cm³ at −180 °C (93 K).[6]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When water freezes, it increases in volume (about 9% for freshwater).[7] The effect of expansion during freezing can be dramatic, and ice expansion is a basic cause of freeze-thaw weathering of rock in nature and damage to building foundations and roadways from frost heaving. It is also a common cause of the flooding of houses when water pipes burst due to the pressure of expanding water when it freezes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of this process is that ice &lt;em&gt;(in its most common form)&lt;/em&gt; floats on liquid water, which is an important feature in Earth’s biosphere. It has been argued that without this property, natural bodies of water would freeze, in some cases permanently, from the bottom up,[8] resulting in a loss of bottom-dependent animal and plant life in fresh and sea water. Sufficiently thin ice sheets allow light to pass through while protecting the underside from short-term weather extremes such as wind chill. This creates a sheltered environment for bacterial and algal colonies. When sea water freezes, the ice is riddled with brine-filled channels which sustain sympagic organisms such as bacteria, algae, copepods and annelids, which in turn provide food for animals such as krill and specialised fish like the bald notothen, fed upon in turn by larger animals such as emperor penguins and minke whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ice melts, it absorbs as much energy as it would take to heat an equivalent mass of water by 80 °C. During the melting process, the temperature remains constant at 0 °C. While melting, any energy added breaks the hydrogen bonds between ice (water) molecules. Energy becomes available to increase the thermal energy (temperature) only after enough hydrogen bonds are broken that the ice can be considered liquid water. The amount of energy consumed in breaking hydrogen bonds in the transition from ice to water is known as the heat of fusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with water, ice absorbs light at the red end of the spectrum preferentially as the result of an overtone of an oxygen-hydrogen (O-H) bond stretch. Compared with water, this absorption is shifted toward slightly lower energies. Thus, ice appears blue, with a slightly greener tint than for liquid water. Since absorption is cumulative, the color effect intensifies with increasing thickness or if internal reflections cause the light to take a longer path through the ice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</guid>
                
                <category>web design</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Review: A Week With the Apple Watch</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/strong&gt; is a smartwatch developed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/&quot;&gt;Apple Inc&lt;/a&gt;. It incorporates fitness tracking and health-oriented capabilities as well as integration with iOS and other Apple products and services. The device is available in four variants: Apple Watch Sport, Apple Watch, Apple Watch Hermès, and Apple Watch Edition. The Watch is distinguished by different combinations of cases and first or third party interchangeable bands. Apple Watch relies on a wirelessly connected iPhone to perform many of its default functions such as calling and texting. It is compatible with the iPhone 5 or later models running iOS 8.2 or later, through the use of Bluetooth or Wi-Fi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Announced by Tim Cook on September 9, 2014, the device was available for pre-order on April 10 and began shipping on April 24, 2015. The Apple Watch quickly became the best-selling wearable device, with the shipment of 4.2 million smartwatches in the second quarter of 2015, according to analyst firm Canalys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“You can only do so many things great, and you should cast aside everything else.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Tim Cook&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumors surrounded an Apple-developed wearable back as far as 2011, which conceptualized the device as a variation of the iPod that would curve around the user’s wrist, and feature Siri integration. On February 10, 2013, both The New York Times and The Wall Street Journal reported that Apple was beginning to develop an iOS-based smartwatch with a curved display. On February 12, 2013, Bloomberg reported that Apple’s smartwatch project was “beyond the experimentation phase in its development”, and had a team of at least 100 designers were working on the project. Further reports in March 2013 indicated that Apple planned to release the device by the end of the year. In July 2013, Financial Times reported that Apple had begun hiring more employees to work on the smartwatch, and that it was targeting a possible retail release in late 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;unveiling--release&quot;&gt;Unveiling &amp;amp; Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In April 2014, Apple CEO &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tim_Cook&quot;&gt;Tim Cook&lt;/a&gt; told The Wall Street Journal that the company was planning to launch new product categories that year, but did not reveal any specifics. In June 2014, Reuters reported that production was expected to begin in July for a release in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch was first unveiled after a classic and ever infamous &lt;em&gt;“We do have ‘one more thing’…”&lt;/em&gt; slide, which heard enormous applause, on September 9, 2014 during a press event which also saw the introduction of the iPhone 6. After the reveal video, the auditorium erupted with applause while Tim Cook rolled back his sleeve, revealing an Apple Watch on his wrist. Speaking about the device, Apple CEO Tim Cook explained that Apple Watch was “a new, intimate way to communicate from your wrist, and a comprehensive health and fitness device.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In comparison to other Apple products and competing smartwatches, marketing of Apple Watch focused more on advertising the device as a fashion accessory; a 12-page advertising spread for Apple Watch in an issue of Vogue focused primarily on the different body and band styles available, and downplayed the technological aspects of it. Apple has also, in particular, focused upon its health and fitness-oriented features, competing against dedicated activity trackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full caption&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/2019/Apple-Watch-In-Car.jpg&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; alt=&quot;Apple Watch&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;Apple watch on the wrist&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;release&quot;&gt;Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-orders for Apple Watch began on April 10, 2015, with an official release on April 24.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On launch, Apple Watch was not available at Apple Store; beginning on April 10, 2015, customers could receive appointments for demonstrations and fitting, but the device was not in-stock for walk-in purchase, and had to be reserved and ordered online (however, sales representatives are able to assist in the process). CNET felt that this distribution model was designed to prevent Apple Store locations from having long line-ups due to high demand. Selected Apple Watch models were available in-store at certain luxury boutiques and authorized Apple resellers in limited quantities. On June 4, 2015, Apple announced that it did plan to stock Apple Watch models at its retail locations. On August 24, 2015 during an earnings call, Best Buy announced that it would begin stocking Apple Watch at its retail stores by the end of September. Both T-Mobile US and Sprint also announced plans to offer Apple Watch through its retail stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Design is a funny word. Some people think design means how it looks. But of course, if you dig deeper, it’s really how it works.” &lt;cite&gt;― Steve Jobs&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015, in Apple’s Special Event, Apple launched a new collection of Apple Watch in a collaboration with Hermès. This new collection of Apple Watch is named as Apple Watch Hermès, comes in stainless steel body with finely crafted leather bands in distinctive styles from Hermès, including the Single Tour, Double Tour and Cuff models. Apple Watch Hermès is available only in selected retail stores of Apple and Hermès.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The device was not branded as “iWatch” (which would put it in line with its other product lines) due to trademark conflicts in certain territories; in the United States, the iWatch trademark is owned by OMG Electronics—who was crowdfunding a device under the same name, and is owned in the European Union by Irish firm Probendi. In July 2015, Probendi sued Apple Inc. for trademark infringement, arguing that through keyword advertising on the Google search engine, it caused advertising for the Apple Watch to appear on search results pages when users searched for the trademarked term “iWatch”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch finally goes on sale in India on Nov. 6. The device also has launched in Chile, the Philippines, and South Africa.  [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Watch&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</guid>
                
                <category>minimal</category>
                
                <category>tech</category>
                
                <category>industrial design</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Basic Rules For Walking In The Mountains</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;em&gt;United States, Canada, the Republic of Ireland, and United Kingdom,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;hiking&lt;/strong&gt; refers to walking outdoors on a trail, or off trail, for recreational purposes. A day hike refers to a hike that can be completed in a single day. However, in the United Kingdom, the word walking is also used, as well as rambling, while walking in mountainous areas is called hillwalking. In Northern England, Including the Lake District and Yorkshire Dales, fellwalking describes hill or mountain walks, as fell is the common word for both features there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hiking can sometimes involves bushwhacking and hiking is sometimes referred to as such. This specifically refers to difficult walking through dense forest, undergrowth, or bushes, where forward progress requires pushing vegetation aside. In extreme cases of bushwhacking, where the vegetation is so dense that human passage is impeded, a machete is used to clear a pathway. The Australian term bushwalking refers to both on and off-trail hiking. Common terms for hiking used by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Zealand&quot;&gt;New Zealanders&lt;/a&gt; are tramping (particularly for overnight and longer trips), walking or bushwalking. Trekking is the preferred word used to describe multi-day hiking in the mountainous regions of India, Pakistan, Nepal, North America, South America, Iran and in the highlands of East Africa. Hiking a long-distance trail from end-to-end is also referred to as trekking and as thru-hiking in some places. In North America, multi-day hikes, usually with camping, are referred to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Backpacking_(wilderness)&quot;&gt;backpacking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;long-distance-hiking&quot;&gt;Long Distance Hiking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frequently nowadays long distance hikes (walking tours) are undertaken along long distance paths, including the National Trails in England and Wales, the National Trail System in the USA and The Grande Randonnée (France), Grote Routepaden, or Lange-afstand-wandelpaden (Holland), Grande Rota (Portugal), Gran Recorrido (Spain) is a network of long-distance footpaths in Europe, mostly in France, Belgium, the Netherlands and Spain. There are extensive networks in other European countries of long distance trails, as well as in Canada, Australia, New Zealand, Nepal, and to a lesser extent other Asiatic countries, like Turkey, Israel, and Jordan. In the Alps of Austria, Slovenia, Switzerland, Germany, France, and Italy walking tours are often made from ‘hut-to-hut’, using an extensive system of mountain huts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full caption&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/2019/Mountain2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; alt=&quot;Mountain&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;Norway is Beautiful&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the late 20th-century there has been a proliferation of official and unofficial long distance routes, which mean that hikers now are more likely to refer to using a long distance way (Britain), trail (USA), The Grande Randonnée (France), etc., than setting out on a walking tour. Early examples of long distance paths, include the Appalachian Trail in the USA and the Pennine Way in Britain. Pilgrimage routes are now treated, by some walkers, as long distance routes, and the route taken by the British National Trail the North Downs Way closely follows that of the Pilgrims’ Way to Canterbury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hiking times can be estimated by Naismith’s rule or Tobler’s hiking function.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;equipment&quot;&gt;Equipment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The equipment required for hiking depends on the length of the hike, but day hikers generally carry at least water, food, a map, and rain-proof gear. Hikers usually wear sturdy hiking boots for mountain walking and backpacking, as protection from the rough terrain, as well as providing increased stability. The Mountaineers club recommends a list of “Ten Essentials” equipment for hiking, including a compass, sunglasses, sunscreen, a flashlight, a first aid kit, a fire starter, and a knife. Other groups recommend items such as hat, gloves, insect repellent, and an emergency blanket. A GPS navigation device can also be helpful and route cards may be used as a guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Cindy Ross&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proponents of ultralight backpacking argue that long lists of required items for multi-day hikes increases pack weight, and hence fatigue and the chance of injury. Instead, they recommend reducing pack weight, in order to make hiking long distances easier. Even the use of hiking boots on long-distances hikes is controversial among ultralight hikers, because of their weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;environmental-impact&quot;&gt;Environmental Impact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Natural environments are often fragile, and may be accidentally damaged, especially when a large number of hikers are involved. For example, years of gathering wood can strip an alpine area of valuable nutrients. and some species, such as martens or bighorn sheep, are very sensitive to the presence of humans, especially around mating season. Generally, protected areas such as parks have regulations in place to protect the environment, so as to minimize such impact. Such regulations include banning wood fires, restricting camping to established camp sites, disposing or packing out faecal matter, and imposing a quota on the number of hikers. Many hikers espouse the philosophy of Leave No Trace, following strict practices on dealing with food waste, food packaging, and other impact on the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Human waste is often a major source of environmental impact from hiking, and can contaminate the watershed and make other hikers ill. ‘Catholes’ dug 10 to 25 cm (4 to 10 inches) deep, depending on local soil composition and covered after use, at least 60 m (200 feet) away from water sources and trails, are recommended to reduce the risk of bacterial contamination. [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hiking&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/basic-rules-for-walking-in-the-mountains</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/basic-rules-for-walking-in-the-mountains</guid>
                
                <category>travel</category>
                
                <category>photography</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>How to Set Up Your New iPhone 6 the Right Way</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 6&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 6 Plus&lt;/strong&gt; are &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smartphone&quot;&gt;smartphones&lt;/a&gt; designed and marketed by Apple Inc. The devices are part of the iPhone series and were unveiled on September 9, 2014, and released on September 19, 2014. The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus jointly serve as successors to the iPhone 5C and iPhone 5S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus include a number of changes over their predecessor, including models with larger 4.7 and 5.5 inches (120 and 140 mm) displays, a faster processor, upgraded cameras, improved LTE and Wi-Fi connectivity and support for a near field communications-based mobile payments offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-orders of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus exceeded four million within its first 24 hours of availability—an Apple record. More than ten million iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus devices were sold in the first three days, another Apple record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015, the 128 GB version of both the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus was discontinued along with the gold version of both phones, but the 16 GB and 64 GB versions of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in silver and space gray remain available for sale at a reduced price due to the release of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_6S&quot;&gt;iPhone 6S and iPhone 6S Plus flagship devices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history&quot;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Centered around the device’s size; the majority of iPhone models have used 3.5-inch displays—which are smaller than screens used by flagship phones from competitors. The last change in size for the iPhone series came with the iPhone 5; the phone and its immediate successors featured a display that was taller, but the same width as prior models, measuring at 4 inches diagonally. Following Apple’s loss in smartphone market share to companies producing phones with larger displays reports as early as January 2014 suggested that Apple was preparing to launch new iPhone models with larger, 4.7-inch and 5.5-inch displays. Reports prior to its unveiling also speculated the possibility that Apple would use a new iPhone model to introduce a mobile payments platform using near-field communications—a technology that has been incorporated into many Android phones, but has experienced a low adoption rate among users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What we want to do is make a leapfrog product that is way smarter than any mobile device has ever been, and super-easy to use. This is what iPhone is. OK? So, we’re going to reinvent the phone. &lt;cite&gt;- Steve Jobs, 2007.&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus were officially unveiled during a press event at the Flint Center for Performing Arts in Cupertino, California on September 9, 2014. The event featured other previously-rumored product announcements by Apple alongside the new iPhone models, including the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Pay&quot;&gt;Apple Pay&lt;/a&gt; mobile payment platform, and the company’s entry into the wearable computing market with the Apple Watch smart watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full caption&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/2019/iPhone-In-Hand.jpg&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; alt=&quot;Apple&quot; /&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;iPhone 6&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus were unveiled on September 9, 2014 and released on September 19, 2014; pre-orders began on September 12, 2014, with the iPhone 6 starting at US$649 and the iPhone 6 Plus starting at US$749. In China, where the iPhone 5S and 5C were the first models in the iPhone series to be released in the country on the same day as their international launch, Apple notified local wireless carriers that it would be unable to release the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in China on the 19th because there were “details which are not ready”; local media reported that the devices had not yet been approved by the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology, and earlier in the year, a news report by state broadcaster China Central Television alleged that iPhone devices were a threat to national security because iOS 7’s “frequent locations” function could expose “state secrets.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 2015 Apple admitted that some iPhone 6 Plus may have faulty cameras that could be causing photos to look blurry and initiated a replacement program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015 the 128 GB version of both the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus was discontinued along with the gold version of both phones, the 16 GB and 64 GB versions of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in silver and space gray remain available for sale at a reduced price due to the release of the iPhone 6S and iPhone 6S Plus flagship devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;specifications&quot;&gt;Specifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The design of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are influenced by that of the iPad Air with a glass front that is curved around the edges of the display, and an aluminum rear that contains two plastic strips for the antenna. Both models come in gold, silver, and “space gray” finishes. The iPhone 6 has a thickness of 6.9 millimetres (0.27 in), while the iPhone 6 Plus is 7.1 mm (0.28 in) in thickness; both are thinner than the iPhone 5S and iPhone 5C, with the iPhone 6 being Apple’s thinnest phone to date. The most significant changes to the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are its displays; both branded as “Retina HD Display” and “ion-strengthened”, the iPhone 6 display is 4.7 inches in size with a 16:9 resolution of 1334x750 (326 PPI, minus one row of pixels), while the iPhone 6 Plus includes a 5.5-inch 1920x1080 (1080p) display (401 PPI). The displays use a multiple-domain LCD panel, dubbed “dual-domain pixels”; the RGB pixels themselves are skewed in pattern, so that every pixel is seen from a different angle. This technique helps improve the viewing angles of the display.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To accommodate the larger physical size of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus, the power button was moved to the side of the phone instead of the top to improve its accessibility. The iPhone 6 features a 6.91 Wh (1810 mAh) battery, while the iPhone 6 Plus features a 11.1 Wh (2915 mAh) battery. Unlike the previous model, the rear-facing camera is not flush with the rear of the device, and has a slight “bulge” around the lens. It has a dual-core 1.4 GHz Cyclone processor (ARM v8-based). [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_6&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/set-up-your-new-iphone-6-the-Right-Way</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/set-up-your-new-iphone-6-the-Right-Way</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>tech</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>The Advantages &amp; Disadvantages of Working from Home</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A work at home parent is an entrepreneur who works from home and integrates parenting into his or her business activities. They are sometimes referred to as a WAHM &lt;em&gt;(work at home mom)&lt;/em&gt; or a WAHD &lt;em&gt;(work at home dad)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneurs choose to run businesses from home for a variety of reasons, including lower business expenses, personal health limitations, eliminating commuting, or in order to have a more flexible schedule. This flexibility can give an entrepreneur more options when planning tasks, business and non-business, including parenting duties. While some home-based entrepreneurs opt for childcare outside the home,[1] others integrate child rearing into their work day and workspace. The latter are considered work-at-home parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many WAHPs start home-based businesses in order to care for their children while still creating income. The desire to care for one’s own children, the incompatibility of a 9-to-5 work day with school hours or sick days, and the expense of childcare prompt many parents to change or leave their jobs in the workforce to be available to their children. Many WAHPs build a business schedule that can be integrated with their parenting duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;concept&quot;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fusion Festival combines all styles of the underground electronic music scene and various other styles, sometimes depending on the attendees who choose to play their own music. It is described as a space people go to free their minds from their everyday lives, jobs, studies and other responsibilities. It is the result of the search for an alternative through music, to the system “people are forced to live in”. People go to the Fusion to experience a different way of socializing and living, where experiencing one another freely, sharing love for music and art connects different scenes and minds. It is a clothing-optional event. Art installations include performance arts, static artworks, sculptures, art cars and various other forms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusion Festival began in 1997 near the city of Lärz in north-eastern Germany, about 160 km from Berlin and 230 km from Hamburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;festival-site&quot;&gt;Festival Site&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location is on the original grass-covered grounds of a disused military airfield (at 53°20′48.11″N 12°44′23.25″E for the 234-hectare area central field) about 4.5 km (2.25 miles) due north of the modern Rechlin-Lärz Airfield facility. The site was first acquired by the German Empire in 1916 as an aviation research and training ground, opening the facility for use by the Luftstreitkräfte in August 1918. After the establishment of the Luftwaffe in 1935, the field served as the Erprobungsstelle Rechlin central military aircraft test facility of the Third Reich through early 1945, and it was captured by the Soviet Red Army on May 2, 1945, for use by the VVS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are grass-covered concrete hangars (actual bunkers) from that time that were used for Soviet fighter aircraft (hence the Cyrillic transliteration of the festival name and various stages, as many Cyrillic inscriptions were still present on the site). The airfield was reopened for civilian use in 1994 and sold to the Müritz Airpark Group in 2010. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fusion_Festival&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>